A Guide to the Edward Ingraham Papers 1980.0035
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series IV: Writings, undated, 1940-1963
  - "Genealogy of Ingraham family", 1962 (Box 21:, Folder 369)
  - George Tetro Interviews, undated (Box 21:, Folder 370)
  - "History of Ingraham Clock Company", 1943 (Box 21:, Folder 371-372)
  - "Industrial Homework", 1962 (Box 21:, Folder 372a)
  - "Lantern Pinion Drilling", 1962 (Box 21:, Folder 373)
  - Letter-press book, 1963 (Box 21:, Folder 374)
  - Memorandum, 1955 (Box 21:, Folder 375)
  - Notes, undated (Box 22:, Folder 376)
  - "Notes on the clock industry", 1962 (Box 22:, Folder 377)
  - Notes on purchasing, 1962 (Box 22:, Folder 378-380)
  - Notes on clockmaking, 1962 (Box 22:, Folder 381-384)
  - "Oakville washers and subdies", 1962 (Box 22:, Folder 385)
  - Original copies of Ingraham papers and drafts, undated (Box 22:, Folder 386-387)
  - Reminiscences of Edward Ingraham, 1938-1962 (Box 22:, Folder 388)
  - Reminiscences of Edward Ingraham, 1938-1962 (Box 23:, Folder 389-394)
  - Talks, speeches, and memorials, undated (Box 23:, Folder 395)
  - Talks, speeches, and memorials, 1940-1954 (Box 23:, Folder 396)
  - "Time Marches On", 1951 (Box 23:, Folder 397)
- Series V: Subject Files, undated, 1787-1969
  - Personal
    - Account Book—Personal Expense, 1919-1926 (Box 23:, Folder 398)
    - Portraits, 1910-1940 (Box 24:, Folder 399)
    - Postcards, undated (Box 24:, Folder 400)
    - Sales analysis, 1935-1942 (Box 24:, Folder 401)
    - School expense ledger, undated (Box 24:, Folder 402)
    - St. Bernard Fish & Game Club, 1959 (Box 24:, Folder 403)
    - Wooden Church Crusade, 1854 (Box 24:, Folder 404)
    - Yale University, 1910-1969 (Box 24:, Folder 405-409)
  - Business
    - Ingraham Inventories, 1931 (Box 25:, Folder 410)
    - Ingraham Company General Instructions 201-265, 1952 (Box 25:, Folder 411)
    - Ingraham Watches and Clocks, 1918-1929 (Box 25:, Folder 412)
    - Manufacturers' Association of Connecticut, undated (Box 25:, Folder 413)
      - News clippings, 1933-1946 (Box 25:, Folder 414)
    - Memoranda, Invoices and Reports, 1909-1939 (Box 25:, Folder 415)
    - Memoranda, Invoices and Reports, 1940-1959 (Box 25:, Folder 416)
    - National Association of Clock and Watch Making Manufacturers, undated, 1948-1957 (Box 25:, Folder 417-418)
    - Negatives, undated (Box 25:, Folder 419)
    - Newspaper clippings
      - E. Ingraham Company, 1931-1962 (Box 25:, Folder 420-421)
      - Family, 1933-196? (Box 25:, Folder 422)
      - McKinley's Death, 1901 (Box 25:, Folder 423)
    - New York Chapter, Yonkers Annual Meeting, 1969 (Box 25:, Folder 424)
  - Business and Connecticut
    - Account Books, 1887-1892 (Box 26:, Folder 425)
    - American Collegiate Institute, 1922 (Box 26:, Folder 426)
    - Army Certificates for E. Ingraham Company, 1917-1919 (Box 26:, Folder 427)
    - Barnum & Bailey Circus Fire, 1944 (Box 26:, Folder 428)
    - Business Meetings, Reports and Minutes, 1930-1947 (Box 26:, Folder 429)
    - College Expense Book, undated (Box 26:, Folder 430)
    - Clockmaking, 1947 (Box 26:, Folder 431)
    - Committee for Reciprocity, 1945 (Box 26:, Folder 432)
    - Congressional Dinner, 1948 (Box 26:, Folder 433)
    - Connecticut Congressional Conference, 1948 (Box 26:, Folder 434)
    - Connecticut Business Directory, 1851 (Box 26:, Folder 435)
    - Connecticut Historical Society, 1966 (Box 26:, Folder 436)
    - Connecticut Scrap Iron and Steel Drive, 1948 (Box 26:, Folder 437)
    - Historical material, undated (Box 26:, Folder 438)
    - Hymne das Marcillais (facsimilie), 1971 (Box 26:, Folder 439)
    - Industrial Playhouse, 1941 (Box 26:, Folder 440)
    - Ingraham Company, undated (Box 26:, Folder 441)
      - Destroyed Correspondence, undated (Box 26:, Folder 442)
      - Documents, 1787-1843 (Box 26:, Folder 443)
      - General Instructions 101-144, undated (Box 26:, Folder 444)
      - General Instructions 145-200, undated (Box 26:, Folder 445)